Contact

164 rue du faubourg Poissonnière 75010 Paris 0686783441 (Mobile) nicolas.genty@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ngenty (LinkedIn) ngenty.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Web Development
User Interface Design
User Experience Design

Languages

English (Professional Working)
French (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Opquast certified : Maîtrise de la qualité en projet Web - 820 points

Nicolas Genty

Webdesigner Freelance

Paris Area, France

Summary

Experienced Web-Designer (10+ years) with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in User Experience (UX), User Interface (UI), Illustration and Icon Design.

Lately I learned front end development at Coding Academy by Epitech.

This training taught me to be autonomous by fetching information, reading documentation to write basic algorithms or working with API.

Today I need an internship to gain experience in order to automate my knowledge and progress to become a full stack designer or even more.

Experience

Freelance Freelance January 2010 - Present

Roi-media webdesigner 2008 - 2010 (3 years)

napao webdesigner January 2006 - January 2008 (2 years 1 month) Paris

Beweb webdesigner September 2001 - May 2004 (2 years 9 months)

Education

Coding Academy by Epitech Front-end development · (2019 - 2019)

Gobelins

· (1999 - 2001)